stitchdata.com 2019-09-14

# Privacy Policy | Stitch

  1. **OUR APPROACH TO PRIVACY**

    1. Stitch, Inc. (“Stitch”, “we”, “our”, or “us”) is strongly committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. This privacy policy sets out how we collect, store, process, transfer, share and use data that identifies or is associated with you (“personal information”) and information regarding our use of cookies and similar technologies.

    2. Stitch operates a platform for moving and modelling data that specifically allows users to provision data from their usual data sources to the data warehouse of their choice, which we make available as a service using our website and web application at [https://www.stitchdata.com](https://www.stitchdata.com/) (the “Service”).

    3. This privacy policy applies to our Service. Terms used in this privacy policy have the same meaning as in our Terms of Service, unless otherwise defined in this privacy policy.

    4. Before accessing or using our Service, please ensure that you have read and understood our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this privacy policy.

    5. Stitch is the data controller of the personal information we hold about you.

  2. **PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU AND HOW WE USE IT**

    1. We collect personal information about you when you voluntarily submit information directly to us when you use our Service. This can include information you provide to us when you register for an account, fill in a form on our Service, create or edit your user profile on the Service, correspond with us by phone, e-mail or otherwise, subscribe to our mailing lists, newsletters or other forms of marketing communications, respond to a survey, enter a promotion or use some other feature of our Service. We may also collect personal information from third parties, such as data enrichment services.

    2. If you choose not to provide personal information, we may not be able to provide the Service to you or respond to your other requests.

    3. The table at **Annex 1** sets out the categories of personal information we collect about you and how we use that information. The table also lists the legal basis which we rely on to process the personal information, the categories of recipients of the personal information and information as to how we determine applicable retention periods.

    4. We also automatically collect personal information about you indirectly about how you access and use the Service and information about the device you use to access the Service.

    5. The table at **Annex 2** sets out the categories of personal information we collect about you automatically and how we use that information. The table also lists the legal basis which we rely on to process the personal information, the categories of recipients of the personal information and information as to how we determine applicable retention periods.

    6. We may link or combine the personal information we collect about you and the information we collect automatically. This allows us to provide you with a personalised experience regardless of how you interact with us.

    7. We may anonymise and aggregate any of the personal information we collect (so that it does not directly identify you). We may use anonymised information for purposes that include testing our IT systems, research, data analysis, improving our Service and developing new products and features. We may also share such anonymised information with others.

  3. **MARKETING AND ADVERTISING**

From time to time we may contact you with information about our products and services. Most marketing messages we send will be by email. For some marketing messages, we may use personal information we collect about you to help us determine the most relevant marketing information to share with you. If you do not want to receive marketing messages from us, you will be able to tell us by selecting certain boxes on forms we use when we first collect your contact details. You can also change your marketing preferences at a later date by clicking on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of our marketing emails or logging into your account on our website and changing your preferences.

  1. **STORING AND TRANSFERRING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

    1. _Security_  
We implement appropriate technical and organisational measures to protect your personal information against accidental or unlawful destruction, loss, change or damage. All personal information we collect will be stored on our secure servers. All electronic transactions entered into via our website will be protected by SSL encryption technology. We will never send you unsolicited emails or contact you by phone requesting your account ID, password, credit or debit card information or national identification numbers.

    2. _International Transfers of your Personal Information_  
As we are located in the USA, any information you provide will initially be collected and stored in the USA. If you are in the EU or EEA, this may mean that your personal information will be stored in a jurisdiction that offers a level of protection that may, in certain instances, be less protective of your personal information than the jurisdiction you are typically resident in.

    3. _Privacy Shield_ We comply with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield framework and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use and retention of personal information received from European Union countries and Switzerland (the “Privacy Shield”). We have certified that we adhere to the Privacy Principles of notice, choice, accountability for onward transfer, security, data integrity, purpose limitation, access, and recourse, enforcement and liability (“Principles”). If there is any conflict between the policies in this Policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Principles shall govern. To learn more about Privacy Shield, please visit the U.S. Department of Commerce Privacy Shield website: <https://www.privacyshield.gov/>. For more information regarding our Privacy Shield certification, please see: <https://www.privacyshield.gov/list>.

    4. If you wish to enquire further about the safeguards we use, please contact us using the details set out at the end of this privacy policy.

    5. We will take reasonable steps to ensure that your personal information is treated securely and in accordance with applicable law and this privacy policy.

  2. **YOUR RIGHTS IN RESPECT OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

    1. In accordance with European Union privacy law, you have the following rights in respect of your personal information that we hold:

      * **Right of access**  
The right to obtain access to your personal information.

      * **Right to rectification**  
The right to obtain rectification of your personal information without undue delay where that personal information is inaccurate or incomplete.

      * **Right to erasure**  
The right to obtain the erasure of your personal information without undue delay in certain circumstances, such as where the personal information is no longer necessary in relation to the purposes for which it was collected or processed.

      * **Right to restriction**  
The right to obtain the restriction of the processing undertaken by us on your personal information in certain circumstances, such as where the accuracy of the personal information is contested by you, for a period enabling us to verify the accuracy of that personal information.

    2. If you wish to exercise one of these rights, please contact us using the contact details at the end of this privacy policy. You may also review and edit the personal information you have submitted to us by logging into your account on our website.

  3. **JURISDICTION AND ENFORCEMENT**

    1. As part of our participation in the Privacy Shield, we are subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the US Federal Trade Commission (FTC).

    2. You also have the right to lodge a complaint to your local data protection authority. Further information about how to contact your local data protection authority is available at [http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/bodies/authorities/index_en.htm](http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/bodies/authorities/index/_en.htm).

    3. In compliance with the EU-US and Swiss-US Privacy Shield Principles, we commit to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. European Union or Swiss individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact us using the contact information listed below.

    4. We have further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the Privacy Shield Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, the BBB EU Privacy Shield Program Under certain conditions specified by the Principles, you may also be able to invoke binding arbitration to resolve your complaint. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed, please visit <http://www.bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers> for more information and to file a complaint.

  4. **COOKIES AND SIMILAR TECHNOLOGIES**

    1. Our website uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our website. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our website and also allows us to improve our website.

    2. Cookies are pieces of code that allow for personalisation of our website experience by saving your information such as user ID and other preferences. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer’s hard disk for record-keeping purposes.

    3. We use the following types of cookies 
      * **Strictly necessary cookies**. These are cookies that are required for the operation of our website. They include, for example, cookies that enable you to log into secure areas of our website, or make use of e-billing services.

      * **Analytical/performance cookies**. They allow us to recognise and count the number of visitors and to see how visitors move around our website when they are using it. This helps us to improve the way our website works, for example, by ensuring that users are finding what they are looking for easily.

      * **Functionality cookies**. These are used to recognise you when you return to our website. This enables us to personalise our content for you, greet you by name and remember your preferences (for example, your choice of language or region).

      * **Targeting cookies**. These cookies record your visit to our website, the pages you have visited and the links you have followed. We will use this information to make our website and the advertising displayed on it, and the marketing messages we send to you more relevant to your interests. We may also share this information with third parties who provide a service to us for this purpose.

      * **Third party cookies**. Please be aware that advertisers and other third parties may use their own cookies tags when you click on an advertisement or link on our website. These third parties are responsible for setting out their own cookie and privacy policies.

    4. **Annex 3** contains more information about the cookies we use and how long they remain on your device.

    5. The cookies we use are designed to help you get the most from the website but if you do not wish to receive cookies, most browsers allow you to change your cookie settings. Please note that if you choose to refuse cookies you may not be able to use the full functionality of our website. These settings will typically be found in the “options” or “preferences” menu of your browser. In order to understand these settings, the following links may be helpful, otherwise you should use the “Help” option in your browser for more details. 
      * Cookie settings in Internet Explorer <https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/products/windows>

      * Cookie settings in Firefox <http://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/cookies>

      * Cookie settings in Chrome <https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en>

      * Cookie settings in Safari on the web <https://support.apple.com/kb/PH5042?locale=en_GB> and iOS <https://support.apple.com/en-gb/HT201265>

    6. If you only want to limit third party advertising cookies, you can turn such cookies off by visiting the following links (please bear in mind that there are many more companies listed on these sites than those that drop cookies via our website): 
      * Your Online Choices <http://www.youronlinechoices.com/>

      * Network Advertising Initiative <http://www.networkadvertising.org/>

      * Digital Advertising Alliance <http://www.aboutads.info/consumers/>

  5. **LINKS TO THIRD PARTY SITES**  
Our Service may, from time to time, contain links to and from third party websites, including those of other users, our partner networks, advertisers, partner merchants, news publications, retailers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for their policies. Please check the individual policies before you submit any information to those websites.

  6. **OUR POLICY TOWARDS CHILDREN**  
Our Service is not directed at persons under 16 and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 16. If you become aware that your child has provided us with personal information, without your consent, then please contact us using the details below so that we can take steps to remove such information and terminate any account your child has created with us.

  7. **CHANGES TO THIS POLICY**  
We may update this privacy policy from time to time and so you should review this page periodically. When we change this privacy policy in a material way, we will update the “last modified” date at the end of this privacy policy. Changes to this privacy policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

  8. **NOTICE TO YOU**  
If we need to provide you with information about something, whether for legal, marketing or other business related purposes, we will select what we believe is the best way to get in contact with you. We will usually do this through email or by placing a notice on our Service. The fact that we may send notices to you will not stop you from being able to opt out of certain types of contact as described in this privacy policy.

  9. **COMPLAINTS**

    1. If you would like to complain about our use of your personal information, please contact us using the details set out at the end of this policy.

    2. If we are unable to resolve your complaint, you can contact BBB Privacy Shield, a non-profit alternative dispute resolution provider located in the United States and operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus, who will attempt to resolve it. Please visit [www.bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers](https://www.bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers) for more information and to file a complaint.

    3. If your complaint remains unresolved, you can refer the matter to the Privacy Shield Panel. Please contact us using the details below if you would like the matter to be handled by the Privacy Shield Panel.

    4. You also have the right to lodge a complaint to your national data protection authority. Further information about how to contact your local data protection authority is available at [http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/bodies/authorities/index_en.htm](http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/bodies/authorities/index/_en.htm)

  10. **CONTACTING US**

    1. Questions, comments and requests regarding this Privacy Policy are welcome and should be sent to [privacy@stitchdata.com](mailto:privacy@stitchdata.com).

    2. This privacy policy was last modified on April 14th, 2018.
